Harry Ammon

50 Cromwell Avenue, Billericay, Essex, CM12 0AG - 07977 864433 - harry a99@hotmail.co.uk

Personal Profile

.NET Developer working for The Pensions Regulator for 3 years. Graduated from the University of Brighton with a Bachelor of Science with First Class Honours in Computer Science. Passionate about solving problems using the latest web technologies and standards.

Technical Skills

- C# .NET Core
- TypeScript
- React
- SASS & CSS3
- HTML5
- RESTful APIs
- SQL
- CI/CD
- Git
- Azure DevOps
- Sitecore
- Umbraco CMS
- TDD

Soft Skills

- Problem Solving
- Kanban
- Communicating technical problems and solutions
- Mentoring

References

Andy Young, IT
Development Manager The Pensions Regulator
Andrew.Young2@tpr.gov.uk

Andrew Montgomery, Personal Tutor – University of Brighton

<u>A.Montgomery@brighton.ac</u> <u>.uk</u>

Mayflower High School educate@mayflowerhigh.es sex.sch.uk

Work Experience

.NET Developer | The Pensions Regulator, Brighton Oct 2021 – Present

Junior .NET Developer | The Pensions Regulator, Brighton Nov 2020 – Oct 2021

Working as part of a large, multidisciplinary team (20), following Kanban principles, to deliver a React Single Page Application, integrated with Sitecore, made with a custom component library. Developed RESTful APIs to integrate the SPA with existing systems. Gained experience and learnt the importance of making websites accessible to everyone.

Working as part of a small team, developed a .NET Core console application which was deployed to all employee computers with integration with SharePoint to assist the business migration from an existing DM system to SharePoint.

Helped train an Intern by having weekly 1:1s.

IT Development Intern | The Pensions Regulator, Brighton Aug 2019 – Nov 2020

Gained professional training in C# and .NET Core building a Console App, a MVC Web App and a RESTful API whilst practicing SOLID principals, dependency injection and Test-Driven-Development (TDD)

Wrote SQL queriers to analyse document metadata in their DM System.

Developed a series of Single Page Applications using React to assist with user testing.

Work experience | JPMorgan & Chase, London Jun 2016

Education

BSc with First Class Honours in Computer Science with Sandwich Year | University of Brighton Sept 2017 – Jun 2021

A Levels | Mayflower High School, Billericay Sept 2015 – Sept 2017 Economics (B) Maths (C) Computer Science (D) EPQ (D)

GCSEs | Mayflower High School, Billericay Sept 2010 – Sept 2015 ICT (A) Maths (B) English Literature (B) English Language (C) Core Science (B) Additional Science (B) Religious Studies (B) Business Studies (B) History (D) Spanish (D)